{
    "subject": "resource/Nancy_Ajram",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Lebanon",
    "human_readable": "Nancy Ajram was born in Lebanon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8620659708976746,
            "question": "Where was Nancy Ajram born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6336665153503418,
            "question": "What nationality is Nancy Ajram?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6154744625091553,
            "question": "What country is associated with Nancy Ajram's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4247290790081024,
            "question": "Are there any famous Lebanese singers besides Nancy Ajram?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20087920129299164,
            "question": "Is Nancy Ajram known for singing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1732781082391739,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Nancy Ajram's musical career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16737280786037445,
            "question": "Has Nancy Ajram achieved musical success?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16291669011116028,
            "question": "Where would you go to listen to Nancy Ajram's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15308663249015808,
            "question": "What genre of music is Nancy Ajram known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14970017969608307,
            "question": "Has Nancy Ajram won any awards for her music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nancy Ajram was born in Lebanon.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9044_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is Nancy Ajram known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9044_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where would you go to listen to Nancy Ajram's music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9044_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Nancy Ajram achieved musical success?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9044_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9044_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9044_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9044_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9044_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9044_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9044_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9044_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9044_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9044_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9044_48.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple to be evaluated is:\n\n\"Was born in Lebanon\"\n\nGiven the context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nReasoning:\n\n* The document at `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9044/re-ranker-msmarco/43.txt` states: \"Born and raised in Lebanon...\"\n* The document at `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9044/re-ranker-msmarco/2.txt` states: \"Born and raised in Lebanon...\"\n* The document at `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9044/re-ranker-msmarco/53.txt` also states: \"Born and raised in Lebanon...\"\n* The document at `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9044/re-ranker-msmarco/39.txt` states: \"born on May 16, 1983, in Beirut, Lebanon\"\n* The document at `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9044/re-ranker-msmarco/42.txt` also states: \"born on May 16, 1983 in Beirut, Lebanon\"\n\nAll documents consistently state that Nancy Ajram was born and raised in Lebanon."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Nancy Ajram was born and raised in Lebanon, which supports the statement that she was born in Lebanon."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}